(Kripke:)How does it work?
(Sheldon:)Oh, it's very simple.
(Sheldon:)Scissors cuts paper,
paper covers rock...
(Sheldon:)...rock crushes lizard,
lizard poisons Spock...
(Sheldon:)...Spock smashes scissors,
scissors decapitates lizard...
(Sheldon:)...lizard eats paper,
paper disproves Spock...
(Sheldon:)...Spock vaporizes rock...
(Sheldon:)...and, as it always has,
rock crushes scissors.
I'm sorry, can you repeat that?
(Sheldon:)Well, of course.
Scissors cuts paper, paper covers rock...
(Sheldon:)...rock crushes lizard,
lizard poisons Spock...
(Sheldon:)...Spock smashes scissors,
scissors decapitates lizard...
(Sheldon:)...lizard eats paper,
paper disproves Spock...
(Sheldon:)...Spock vaporizes rock...
(Sheldon:)...and, as it always has,
rock crushes scissors.
(Kripke:)Almost got it. One more time.
(Sheldon:)Scissors cuts paper,
paper covers rock...
(Howard:)Sheldon, stop.
He's screwing with you.
ls he?
(Sheldon:)Well, then,
seems we have reached an impasse.
l see no other option
than to challenge you to a duel.